# **BRANDON JIMENEZ**

## CYBER SECURITY PROFESSIONAL

#### CAREER OBJECTIVE

Cyber Security Professional with a passion for all things technology, system administration and information security; with 4 years of experience in troubleshooting and supporting a variety of systems. Looking to bring my knowledge gained through certifications, self-study, and professional experience to a Cybersecurity Analyst role within your company.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

September 2021–Present | Kiewit Corporation, Omaha, NE Cyber Security Analyst

Focus on security operations, incident response and threat intelligence.

- Ensure monitoring of alerts and logs from enterprise security tools such as firewalls, IDS, Anti-virus, Data Loss Protection (DLP) and vulnerability scanners
- Utilizing LogRhythm and Microsoft Defender, incident response and threat analysis
- Perform cyber news analysis, security awareness training and recommend new analytic methods for detecting threats
- Documenting and conforming to processes related to security monitoring and detection
- Prioritizing workflow; addressing technical and non-technical escalations to satisfaction

October 2018–September 2021 | Kiewit Corporation, Omaha, NE **Technology Group Senior Service Technician** 

Responsible for preparing and shipping PCs to Kiewit's end users based on information submitted through our internal ticket system. Focused primarily on the tactical elements of PC diagnostics, repair, and imaging.

- Project Management Lead for troubleshooting efficiencies, operations, and maintenance
- Revitalized Knowledge Base Troubleshooting and Team Policies
- Audited software logs to ensure documented guidelines for team process are in line within specifications
- Analysed and addressed severe hardware issues
- Followed established processes for imaging and repairing computers
- Maintained and tracked available PC inventory for a significant portion of the Kiewit Technology Group.

November 2017-October 2018 | First Data, Omaha, NE

## **Contact Center Technical Specialist**

While working for First Data (now Fiserv) I was responsible for performing routine merchant account-related transactions and was the main point of contact for issues with point-of-sale systems. During my tenure I was promoted to Web Portal Payment Support due to my technical proficiency and troubleshooting ability.

- Investigated and resolved a wide variety of technical issues and requests relating to point-of-sale systems
- Dynamically upheld PCI Compliance
- Managed inbound calls for software and point-of-sale systems
- Incident management; restoring services within agreed SLAs
- Disseminated complex information to tech users of all abilities

•

(201) 878-2573



brandonjimzz@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/brandon-jimenez

#### **EDUCATION**

November 2018

Metropolitan Community College Omaha, NE

Associate in Applied Science, Server Administration

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

CompTIA Cybersecurity Analyst+

CompTIA Security+

CompTIA Network+

LogRhythm Security Analyst

### **RELEVANT SKILLS**

Incident Response

**Building Secure Environments** 

Data Security

**Security Policies** 

Threat Intelligence

Vulnerability Management

Virtualization

Inventory Management

Network/System Troubleshooting

## PERSONAL DEVELOPMENT

Home Lab

- Homebrew KB to document design and configuration
- VMs for learning Windows Server, Ubuntu, Fedora and Kali Linux; virtual networking
- Penetration testing